{
    "id": "7fdcee6ee4734e0ebf8960f3b8b91a6e",
    "title": "I Wish, I'd Rather, I'd Better",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I would rather you ........................... at me.",
            "description": "After would rather, we use a past tense with a present meaning. ",
            "answers": [
                "don't shout",
                "didn't shout"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "08c61f8a441f426798adfa9301bdc853"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish I ........................ work on Saturdays.",
            "description": "After I wish, we use a past tense with present meaning. ",
            "answers": [
                "don't have to",
                "didn't have to",
                "hadn't to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "98ae1ff67b454ad9b0387ad0760e879d"
        },
        {
            "question": "You'd better ....................... me my money back.",
            "description": "After had better, we use the infinitive without to (first form of the verb).",
            "answers": [
                "give",
                "gave",
                "given"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fd75bd57e42c41538b6c071aa79cabeb"
        },
        {
            "question": "After the way he behaved at my party, I wish I ......................... him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "didn't invite",
                "don't invite",
                "hadn't invited"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "836e93c8bb4d457089ad04937da96c87"
        },
        {
            "question": "I'd rather ........................... up early on Sundays.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "not get",
                "don't get",
                "didn't get"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "45c83bfed6b3461f8519954d75d73713"
        },
        {
            "question": "The program starts at 6 o'clock. You had better ..................... late.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "not be",
                "not to be",
                "be not"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7b5c2d3050b642ad9b36b6bb7621319e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I'd rather you ........................... on Tuesday than Monday.",
            "description": "After would rather, we use a past tense with present meaning. ",
            "answers": [
                "come",
                "came",
                "had come"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "33d1f38cbf5a48979969f3d8dfe7ee8e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish I ............................. to work tomorrow.",
            "description": "After I wish, we use a past tense with present meaning. ",
            "answers": [
                "don't have",
                "didn't have",
                "won't have"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a1c190385b614ce3bbecf2e3c376ad32"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish you …………………. insist on leaving early.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "won't",
                "wouldn't",
                "hadn't"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e53b5c3270c24e4e99f45d613f7ca6a0"
        },
        {
            "question": "You'd better ........................... him with your crude jokes.",
            "description": "After had better, we use an infinitive without to. Negative forms are made by putting not before the infinitive. ",
            "answers": [
                "not offend",
                "to not offend",
                "not to offend"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "416ff67f9028497ab21899db259992e4"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish I ........................... get a scholarship.",
            "description": "A past tense is used with present meaning after would rather. ",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b4bd6be030fd4e5489ec936cd25e3434"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish you .............................. leave me alone.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d9ab6c1fb31644558133c4bcf8cd8683"
        }
    ]
}